<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Waterford City Viqueens on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/waterford-city-viqueens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Waterford City Viqueens on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/waterford-city-viqueens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Derby Round-Up: March</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-round-up-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-round-up-march/</guid>
      <description>After a very busy February, things are a little quieter this month, but there&amp;#8217;s still plenty to whet your Derby appetite. Most of the action is concentrated around the weekend of the 11/12th and it&amp;#8217;s from there we&amp;#8217;ll take a look at the spotlight game of the month.
Spotlight Game: LRD A vs DRD A On Saturday 12th March, Limerick Roller Derby is hosting Dublin Roller Derby A team. In Greystones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Derby Tournament this weekend!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-tournament-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-tournament-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, Greystones and the East Coast Cyclones will play host to only the second ever roller derby tournament to be held on Irish soil. The last one was in Belfast and was an absolute belter &amp;#8211; with Dublin Roller Derby A coming home the overall winners &amp;#8211; with Belfast Roller Derby in second place and Limerick Roller Derby in third.
This, Queen Bee Tournament, The Battle for the Garden, is focussed on the B-teams and the newer, less-established teams in the country and will feature the host team, Belfast City Rockets, Boom Town Rollers from Dublin, Dublin Roller Derby B and the Waterford City Viqueens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>