<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 20:26:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A guide to Facebook Competitions and how to avoid the scams</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/a-guide-to-facebook-competitions-and-how-to-avoid-the-scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 20:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/a-guide-to-facebook-competitions-and-how-to-avoid-the-scams/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been using Facebook for far too many years now, and one thing that is perennial is people sharing competitions in the hope that they will be one of the lucky ones that will win a car or a holiday or a brand new iPhone. However, a lot of these competitions are fake and are aimed at folks who may not be savvy about how to spot a scam. Here are my top tips for things to check BEFORE you click like or share!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Static </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/moving-to-static/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/moving-to-static/</guid>
      <description>I don’t blog very often. Calling me a sporadic blogger would be overly generous. I’ve probably used Facebook for much of my longer-length bits and pieces over the past few years. On Thursday I’d a day off work and wrote a diatribe about the scourge of “like and share” scams on Facebook. I posted it to Facebook, where it got surprisingly little traction (maybe because I was being patronising, maybe because people only share nonsense on Facebook, not anything useful).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Audio – a solution to a problem you didn’t know you had</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-11-match-audio-a-solution-to-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-had/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-11-match-audio-a-solution-to-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-had/</guid>
      <description>_Match Audio is a new music-sharing app created by Jonathan Cremin aka @kudoz aka my boyfriend. I take a look at how to use match.audio and why &amp;#8211; and chat with the dev about his plans for its future._
With more and more people turning to subscription sites to explore new music, the way we listen to and consume music has undergone another radical change. It’s easier to find and it’s easier to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>[][1]Happy Rails Girls (and boys) after the workshop Photo by Serena Fritsch I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting around Dublin: three essential Android apps…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-around-dublin-three-essential-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 12:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-around-dublin-three-essential-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>So, you’ve just moved to Dublin and you’re trying to make sense of the public transport system. Don’t bother. The two Luas lines, the bus system and the Dart and rail systems are all pretty much independent of each other.Leap Card
What I recommend you do &amp;#8211; get yourself a Leap card. The fares are a little cheaper, you don’t have to worry about carrying cash, and it’ll work on all public transport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycon ’09 Initial reaction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/skycon-09-initial-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/skycon-09-initial-reaction/</guid>
      <description>I am still in bed after the weekend. I pity those that had to get up to travel/get flights etc.
Initial reactions over the weekend were that it was lovely, lovely, lovely to see all of these people again, the day of the conference itself went very well, the nights went better, and that I should have gotten more sleep on friday night.
Also, CAKE!! (pic by colmmacc)

The Cake, projected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I just wandered in, I’m not a geek I swear. And now I can’t get home!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/i-just-wandered-in-im-not-a-geek-i-swear-and-now-i-cant-get-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2007 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/i-just-wandered-in-im-not-a-geek-i-swear-and-now-i-cant-get-home/</guid>
      <description>I was at Wolverhampton at the weekend with the Skynet kids for Lugradio Live 2007.  Despite my immense lack of knowledge of Free/Open Source Software, and my non-contribution to the FOSS community; the amount of fun that was had in the company of the Lugradio lads during Skycon in February (sub-par knob jokes notwithstanding) meant that I decided to make the trek to Wolverhampton to see the boys and possibly have some fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>