<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dunedin on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dunedin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dunedin on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2005 13:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dunedin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Elusive Dunedin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/672/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2005 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/672/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t quite seem to get a handle on Dunedin. I&amp;#8217;m not sure why, but it sort of eludes me. Maybe it&amp;#8217;s because most of the students aren&amp;#8217;t here, and there are usually around 25,000 of them? I&amp;#8217;m not sure, but I think I could possibly like this town, once I get the hang of it.
Granted, it took me a lot longer than four days to get the hang of Auckland, but this place is so much smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Chinese New Year!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/happy-chinese-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2005 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/happy-chinese-new-year/</guid>
      <description>I completely forgot about the pancakes yesterday, but last night at midnight there were the coolest fireworks to celebrate Chinese New Year. It&amp;#8217;s good that NZ sometimes remembers that it&amp;#8217;s closer to Asia than Europe. Also yesterday I wandered around the Museum, which was partially closed due to flooding from the excellent rains the day before. As were quite a few shops in the city centre.
I would say more, but I&amp;#8217;m sure you don&amp;#8217;t care that it was a little bit chilly last night, that I had tuna and cheese on toast for dinner or that I did my laundry and watched survivor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Again with the Dunedin and the Sunshine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/again-with-the-dunedin-and-the-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2005 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/again-with-the-dunedin-and-the-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was moderately uneventful, except that when I left the internet cafe there was a massive black cloud obscuring all light, and I eventually got caught in the mother of all downpours. It was great. Thunder, lightening, massive raindrops and rivers instead of streets! I got back to the hostel and was so soaking wet that I put my bag down and ran straight back out again.
Fantastic!
Today I got offered a lift to invercargill with two swiss chicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunedin, Sunshine and Dreamcatchers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dunedin-sunshine-and-dreamcatchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2005 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dunedin-sunshine-and-dreamcatchers/</guid>
      <description>Good afternoon,
Yesterday I arrived in Dunedin, proceeded to get lost, (which is never a good idea with a backpack that&amp;#8217;s too heavy), get found, went online to check my mail and update here, couldn&amp;#8217;t check my mail cos none of the websites would open, managed to open LJ and typed up a major updatey post on getting drunk and misbehaving, leaving christchurch, lake tekapo and the unbelievable gorgeousness, oamaru and limestone and small-town-ness and penguins and tour buses, and weird nightmares about fountains and collapsing buildings, and tried to post it and it died, which was the computer&amp;#8217;s fault, not mine&amp;#8230; and i had to pay $4 for the privilege of NOT BEING ABLE TO CHECK MY MAIL and GETTING UPSET THAT MY UPDATE GOT EATEN.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>