<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adventures on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/adventures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in adventures on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 2 – The Drugs sometimes Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on the topic of the different treatments I&amp;#8217;ve been on for Depression &amp; Anxiety. I&amp;#8217;m looking at the different types of drugs I was prescribed and I might also tell you how I really feel about people&amp;#8217;s attitude to medicating for depression. Before I say anything else, a disclaimer. These are the drugs I was prescribed, these are the effects and side-effects I personally had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>[][1]Happy Rails Girls (and boys) after the workshop Photo by Serena Fritsch I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gael Fours – Four Roller Derby Games  in ONE DAY!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gael-fours-four-roller-derby-games-in-one-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 12:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gael-fours-four-roller-derby-games-in-one-day/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve ever been curious about Roller Derby, come to the Shoreline Leisure Centre in Bray this Saturday. You&amp;#8217;ll see four games &amp;#8211; including a co-ed and a men&amp;#8217;s game!
The worst thing about the increase in the popularity of roller derby in Ireland is the fact that sometimes events clash and you end up having to miss something you were really looking forward to.
Dublin Roller Derby had invited me to announce at their upcoming double-header against Newcastle Roller Derby&amp;#8217;s Canny Belters and Hull&amp;#8217;s Angels Roller Dames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roller Derby Tournament this weekend!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-tournament-this-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 19:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/roller-derby-tournament-this-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, Greystones and the East Coast Cyclones will play host to only the second ever roller derby tournament to be held on Irish soil. The last one was in Belfast and was an absolute belter &amp;#8211; with Dublin Roller Derby A coming home the overall winners &amp;#8211; with Belfast Roller Derby in second place and Limerick Roller Derby in third.
This, Queen Bee Tournament, The Battle for the Garden, is focussed on the B-teams and the newer, less-established teams in the country and will feature the host team, Belfast City Rockets, Boom Town Rollers from Dublin, Dublin Roller Derby B and the Waterford City Viqueens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Street Harassment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 00:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</guid>
      <description>I stood up to a street harasser yesterday and I&amp;#8217;m glad I did. Here&amp;#8217;s a fuller version of the story.
First, some context:
A train full of people returning from a sporting event is an experience. I got the train from Limerick to Dublin yesterday and the first leg was full of Cork and Limerick supporters on their way home. I was on the train 15 minutes before departure and there were only a few empty seats dotted around the carriages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooray for Perfect Days</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hooray-for-perfect-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2005 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hooray-for-perfect-days/</guid>
      <description>Today was just such a one.
Waking up early but not too early. Luxuriating in bed for just a little bit. Having a shower, a proper shower with gushing jets of not too hot, not too cold water. Strolling to the French Bakehouse for breakfast and up to Captain Ron&amp;#8217;s for coffee. Making a new friend or two. Deciding to go for a stroll Just Like That. Finding out how much it costs to rent an MX5 for a day and pretend to be Austin Powers(not that much really).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh! November!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2004 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</guid>
      <description>Buggerit! I really am working for the man. GE donated $2.58million to the US Republican party since 1999. Yuk. I&amp;#8217;m finishing in 2 weeks though, so that&amp;#8217;ll stick it to them. Yeah! And I stole about 20 helium balloons today, all printed with GE Money, which is what GE finance is now called in New Zealand. So I&amp;#8217;ve made them scared now, I&amp;#8217;ll bet.
In other news, there has been much fun and also some sleep had.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>