<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adventures on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/adventures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in adventures on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 2 – The Drugs sometimes Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on the topic of the different treatments I&amp;#8217;ve been on for Depression &amp;amp; Anxiety. I&amp;#8217;m looking at the different types of drugs I was prescribed and I might also tell you how I really feel about people&amp;#8217;s attitude to medicating for depression.
Before I say anything else, a disclaimer. These are the drugs I was prescribed, these are the effects and side-effects I personally had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin. I knew it would be an encouraging atmosphere where I could get some basic information, and I&amp;#8217;d heard that Ruby on Rails was a good starting point for a programming newbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Street Harassment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 00:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</guid>
      <description>I stood up to a street harasser yesterday and I&amp;#8217;m glad I did. Here&amp;#8217;s a fuller version of the story.
First, some context: A train full of people returning from a sporting event is an experience. I got the train from Limerick to Dublin yesterday and the first leg was full of Cork and Limerick supporters on their way home. I was on the train 15 minutes before departure and there were only a few empty seats dotted around the carriages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooray for Perfect Days</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hooray-for-perfect-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2005 23:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hooray-for-perfect-days/</guid>
      <description>Today was just such a one.
Waking up early but not too early. Luxuriating in bed for just a little bit. Having a shower, a proper shower with gushing jets of not too hot, not too cold water. Strolling to the French Bakehouse for breakfast and up to Captain Ron&amp;#8217;s for coffee. Making a new friend or two. Deciding to go for a stroll Just Like That. Finding out how much it costs to rent an MX5 for a day and pretend to be Austin Powers(not that much really).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh! November!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2004 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</guid>
      <description>Buggerit! I really am working for the man. GE donated $2.58million to the US Republican party since 1999. Yuk. I&amp;#8217;m finishing in 2 weeks though, so that&amp;#8217;ll stick it to them. Yeah! And I stole about 20 helium balloons today, all printed with GE Money, which is what GE finance is now called in New Zealand. So I&amp;#8217;ve made them scared now, I&amp;#8217;ll bet.
In other news, there has been much fun and also some sleep had.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>