<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>women on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/women/</link>
    <description>Recent content in women on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin. I knew it would be an encouraging atmosphere where I could get some basic information, and I&amp;#8217;d heard that Ruby on Rails was a good starting point for a programming newbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Street Harassment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 00:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</guid>
      <description>I stood up to a street harasser yesterday and I&amp;#8217;m glad I did. Here&amp;#8217;s a fuller version of the story.
First, some context: A train full of people returning from a sporting event is an experience. I got the train from Limerick to Dublin yesterday and the first leg was full of Cork and Limerick supporters on their way home. I was on the train 15 minutes before departure and there were only a few empty seats dotted around the carriages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuntbuckets, Mooncups and how I learned to stop worrying and love my period (kinda)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cuntbuckets-mooncups-and-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-my-period-kinda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cuntbuckets-mooncups-and-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-my-period-kinda/</guid>
      <description>This post is aimed at people who menstruate. It may be interesting to those who don&amp;#8217;t, but if you complain about it being about menstruation having read it, I&amp;#8217;m going to mock you.
The awesome mooncup plushie in the featured image is by [Unicorn Reality][(https://www.deviantart.com/unicornreality)]
I&amp;#8217;ve been hearing about the next great leap in feminine hygiene (now there&amp;#8217;s a phrase I hate with a passion) for quite a few years now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The paper of note took note.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-paper-of-note-took-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-paper-of-note-took-note/</guid>
      <description>For the last week, I&amp;#8217;ve been equally upset and outraged by the case of Savita Halappanavar, who died in Galway on October 28th after contracting septicaemia following a drawn-out miscarriage. The medical team waited until the foetal heart stopped beating before removing the foetus, even though risk of infection was extremely high. I&amp;#8217;ve contacted my local TDs (only one had the decency to respond so far) and stood outside the Dáil with crowds of people twice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>