<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 16:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Audio – a solution to a problem you didn’t know you had</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-11-match-audio-a-solution-to-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-had/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2015 16:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2015-01-11-match-audio-a-solution-to-a-problem-you-didnt-know-you-had/</guid>
      <description>_Match Audio is a new music-sharing app created by Jonathan Cremin aka @kudoz aka my boyfriend. I take a look at how to use match.audio and why &amp;#8211; and chat with the dev about his plans for its future._
With more and more people turning to subscription sites to explore new music, the way we listen to and consume music has undergone another radical change. It’s easier to find and it’s easier to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DRM-free music to become more common?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/935/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2007 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/935/</guid>
      <description> From ArtsJournal and BBC News &amp;#8211; (See Article) Universal Music is experimenting with the idea of selling CDs and MP3s that do not contain copy-protection technology that has enraged consumer groups and sparked arguments over fair use. &amp;#8220;Retailers including Google, Wal-Mart, and Amazon.com, will participate in the DRM-free trial, Universal said. But participants do not include Apple iTunes online music store, the third largest music retailer in the US.&amp;#8221; BBC 08/10/07  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Bagpipes Batman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte and I were just wandering around town, checking out secondhand bookshops and having coffee and being exhausted and stuff, and then BAM, the octagon is filled with HORDES of bagpipers. there&amp;#8217;s some kind of competition on today I think.
THe best bit was at the end where about eight bands lined up together and all marched down George St playing Scotland the Brave. Stirring indeed. No matter who you are or where you&amp;#8217;re from, a bazillion bagpipers going right past your ear is an unforgettable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>