<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books and Reading on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/books-and-reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books and Reading on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2007 13:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/books-and-reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the End of the World (I’m done now, I swear!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/harry-potter-and-the-end-of-the-world-im-done-now-i-swear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2007 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/harry-potter-and-the-end-of-the-world-im-done-now-i-swear/</guid>
      <description>It’s been fun, since Saturday, waiting for people to finish The Book That Shall Not Be Named so that we could huddle in dark corners to discuss it without hysterical accusations of spoiling. I even set up an IRC channel on intersocs, and people have been dribbling in, saying “I can’t believe it’s over” and then leaving.
It’s odd. There are so many books out there, so many series of books, some of which are awful, but many of which are as good, and some of which are a LOT better than the Harry Potter series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obligatory, pretty much, Harry Potter Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/obligatory-pretty-much-harry-potter-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/obligatory-pretty-much-harry-potter-post/</guid>
      <description>In a bizarre turn-up for the books, it’s raining again. I’ve never been particularly bothered by the lack of summery weather before, but there’s something so depressing about the almost inevitable fact that everything this summer is going to get rained out and ruined.
I’m still finding it difficult to feel sorry for the people apparently queuing outside Eason’s bookshop since this morning in order to get their hands on the new Harry Potter book when it comes out at MinutePastMidnightO’Clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serendipity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/serendipity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/serendipity/</guid>
      <description>Many things give me joy:
I found a bookcrossing book! My first one ever! It&amp;#8217;s Bee Season by Myla Goldberg, and I&amp;#8217;m just about to release Riddley Walker into the wild. Or rather, into a phone box! It&amp;#8217;s the best plan ever. And the karma feels great!
It&amp;#8217;s SUNNY
I&amp;#8217;m going to check out penguins in an hour&amp;#8230; well, less than an hour&amp;#8230; and I haven&amp;#8217;t packed yet, even though I&amp;#8217;m leaving tomorrow morning at a rediculous time of the day&amp;#8230; er&amp;#8230; yes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Bagpipes Batman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte and I were just wandering around town, checking out secondhand bookshops and having coffee and being exhausted and stuff, and then BAM, the octagon is filled with HORDES of bagpipers. there&amp;#8217;s some kind of competition on today I think.
THe best bit was at the end where about eight bands lined up together and all marched down George St playing Scotland the Brave. Stirring indeed. No matter who you are or where you&amp;#8217;re from, a bazillion bagpipers going right past your ear is an unforgettable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rip Van Winkle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rip-van-winkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2005 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rip-van-winkle/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;#8217;t you just love the feeling you get when you&amp;#8217;ve been engrossed in a book for hours and you&amp;#8217;ve completely disregarded reality, to the point that you&amp;#8217;ve forgotten that there&amp;#8217;s someone else in the room, and you finish the book and it feels like you&amp;#8217;ve been asleep for a hundred years?
It&amp;#8217;s a sort of a poignant, satisfied sort of feeling. You&amp;#8217;re glad you&amp;#8217;ve read what you&amp;#8217;ve been reading, but you want to stay in the moments created by the author and you know you can&amp;#8217;t.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>