<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>programming on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in programming on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Static</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/moving-to-static/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/moving-to-static/</guid>
      <description>I don’t blog very often. Calling me a sporadic blogger would be overly generous. I’ve probably used Facebook for much of my longer-length bits and pieces over the past few years. On Thursday I’d a day off work and wrote a diatribe about the scourge of “like and share” scams on Facebook. I posted it to Facebook, where it got surprisingly little traction (maybe because I was being patronising, maybe because people only share nonsense on Facebook, not anything useful).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin. I knew it would be an encouraging atmosphere where I could get some basic information, and I&amp;#8217;d heard that Ruby on Rails was a good starting point for a programming newbie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>