<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mental Health on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mental Health on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures In Therapy: Part 3 – Insomnia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-3-insomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-3-insomnia/</guid>
      <description>What I’ve learned about dealing with Insomnia &amp;amp; Anxiety. A terrible twosome, these two conditions can go hand in hand, often with Depression rounding out the trifecta. It could be finding it hard to go to sleep because of racing thoughts and elevated heartbeat or just lying awake in the middle the night worrying about everything that has happened, might happen or should have happened. And of course there’s the anxiety of “I should be asleep, I’m not asleep and NOW I AM ANXIOUS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 2 – The Drugs sometimes Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on the topic of the different treatments I&amp;#8217;ve been on for Depression &amp;amp; Anxiety. I&amp;#8217;m looking at the different types of drugs I was prescribed and I might also tell you how I really feel about people&amp;#8217;s attitude to medicating for depression.
Before I say anything else, a disclaimer. These are the drugs I was prescribed, these are the effects and side-effects I personally had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 1 – Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>I’m planning a blog series. This has never ended well before now, but I’m going to try again anyway.
So this is the introductory post to….. Drumroll
Adventures in Therapy! I’m planning to outline the different therapies I’ve availed of &amp;#8211; both medical and non-medical and what has worked for me. And probably also get angry at people who have internalised the stigma even though I should feel sorry for them 🙂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to talk?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/time-to-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 09:34:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/time-to-talk/</guid>
      <description>Today is Time to Talk Day in Ireland, organised by the Green Ribbon Project
We’re making great strides in encouraging people with mental health difficulties, people who are struggling and people who are overwhelmed to reach out to someone and break the silence. From personal experience both as the reacher and the reachee, I wanted to share some tips on how to be reached out to.
The first step is Time It can be difficult to open up to someone and this is doubly true if it’s the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>me – in a slightly stale, undelicious nutshell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/me-in-a-slightly-stale-undelicious-nutshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/me-in-a-slightly-stale-undelicious-nutshell/</guid>
      <description>You know those montages in silly Hollywood movies where one character lets themselves go completely and sits around watching daytime tv and eating cereal and wearing pyjamas/tracksuits all day with messy hair and an ever-expanding waistline? That&amp;#8217;s me. For the past four and a half months, since my contract wasn&amp;#8217;t renewed at the place were I worked and loved it, I&amp;#8217;ve been a Hollywood stereotype. And yes, I&amp;#8217;m listening to Rachmaninov&amp;#8217;s second piano concerto at the moment too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>