<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mental health on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mental health on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:02:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures In Therapy: Part 3 – Insomnia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-3-insomnia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-3-insomnia/</guid>
      <description>What I’ve learned about dealing with Insomnia &amp;amp; Anxiety. Picture by Basel Mahmoud (from Deviant Art)
A terrible twosome, these two conditions can go hand in hand, often with Depression rounding out the trifecta. It could be finding it hard to go to sleep because of racing thoughts and elevated heartbeat or just lying awake in the middle the night worrying about everything that has happened, might happen or should have happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 2 – The Drugs sometimes Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on the topic of the different treatments I&amp;#8217;ve been on for Depression &amp; Anxiety. I&amp;#8217;m looking at the different types of drugs I was prescribed and I might also tell you how I really feel about people&amp;#8217;s attitude to medicating for depression. Before I say anything else, a disclaimer. These are the drugs I was prescribed, these are the effects and side-effects I personally had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 1 – Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-1-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 14:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-1-introduction/</guid>
      <description>I’m planning a blog series. This has never ended well before now, but I’m going to try again anyway. So this is the introductory post to….. *Drumroll* Adventures in therapy! {.p1} I’m planning to outline the different therapies I’ve availed of &amp;#8211; both medical and non-medical and what has worked for me. And probably also get angry at people who have internalised the stigma even though I should feel sorry for them 🙂 Here goes… I’m a person with depression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>