<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 16:41:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection, roots and rapid-fire ideas.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reflection-roots-and-rapid-fire-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reflection-roots-and-rapid-fire-ideas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s official. I&amp;#8217;m finally a Dubliner (or whatever it is that real Dublin people call blow-ins from down the country). I&amp;#8217;ve handed back the keys to my lovely apartment in Limerick and torn up as many Limerick roots as I can, or want to (Ancór and Limerick Roller Girls 4 LYFE!). I now live in The Smoke that is bigger than the other Smokes on this tiny island. I am cohabiting with Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Start Continues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-new-start-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 16:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-new-start-continues/</guid>
      <description>Change is good, right?
&amp;nbsp;
I’ve changed a LOT of things in the last six weeks. I’ve moved city, shacked up with my lovely man, left my job of six years (on and off, mostly on) and started a course in Digital Marketing with a view to a career change.
  It’s been a period of rushing, rearranging and reviewing. I’ve gotten used to the DART timetables and using my Leap card (which I’ve had since I lived in Limerick &amp;#8211; very early adopter indeed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hangover?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hangover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2010 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hangover/</guid>
      <description>Hangover?, originally uploaded by La Froodie.  I took this pic last summer at my parents&amp;#8217; house. My brother had had a party the night before, and clearly decided to be responsible about the recycling. Or else there&amp;#8217;s a better story. Any ideas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>me – in a slightly stale, undelicious nutshell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/me-in-a-slightly-stale-undelicious-nutshell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/me-in-a-slightly-stale-undelicious-nutshell/</guid>
      <description>You know those montages in silly Hollywood movies where one character lets themselves go completely and sits around watching daytime tv and eating cereal and wearing pyjamas/tracksuits all day with messy hair and an ever-expanding waistline? That&amp;#8217;s me. For the past four and a half months, since my contract wasn&amp;#8217;t renewed at the place were I worked and loved it, I&amp;#8217;ve been a Hollywood stereotype. And yes, I&amp;#8217;m listening to Rachmaninov&amp;#8217;s second piano concerto at the moment too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection, by Sarah</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reflection-by-sarah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reflection-by-sarah/</guid>
      <description>Reflection, by Sarah, originally uploaded by colmmacc.  Colmmacc is really as good at cropping photos as he is at taking them. We were driving around Galway at the weekend, and I was snapping away as he drove. He&amp;#8217;s put some of my snaps up on his flickr, and I&amp;#8217;m surprised at how well some of them turned out. Maybe I should buy a *cough* SLR *cough*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FClock</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fclock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 06:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fclock/</guid>
      <description>FClock, originally uploaded by La Froodie.  I&amp;#8217;ve been on a real &amp;#8216;making crap&amp;#8217; kick lately. I&amp;#8217;ve not felt like buying stuff, and am really getting into making gifts for people. This is the last one I made, for le boy&amp;#8217;s birthday, which is on Thursday.
He seems to like it too, which I was sort of hoping for, given his penchant for geeky clocks and the colour green. In fact, I enjoyed making this so much that I&amp;#8217;m tempted to buy a bunch of mechanisms on ebay and go crazy making clocks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycon ’09 Initial reaction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/skycon-09-initial-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2009 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/skycon-09-initial-reaction/</guid>
      <description>I am still in bed after the weekend. I pity those that had to get up to travel/get flights etc.
Initial reactions over the weekend were that it was lovely, lovely, lovely to see all of these people again, the day of the conference itself went very well, the nights went better, and that I should have gotten more sleep on friday night.
Also, CAKE!! (pic by colmmacc)

The Cake, projected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doggone…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/doggone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/doggone/</guid>
      <description>This is Socks. She&amp;#8217;s been my dog for the last 13 years. She was very small, very cute, very mono-ocular, very snuggly and very smelly from time to time. She loved begging for food, going for walks, sleeping and whoring round the neighbours for food, walks and cuddles. When it was time for dinner, she would run up and down our hall, doing 360-degree spins of excitement and grunting with joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So… birthdays…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/so-birthdays/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/so-birthdays/</guid>
      <description>So, I&amp;#8217;m older than I was&amp;#8230; &amp;nbsp;the year counter racheted up one more notch on Sunday. The entire weekend was spent celebrating, which was kind of nice&amp;#8230; I think I&amp;nbsp;like the thoughts of a birthday weekend. There was choir, and guinness, and dancing in awful clubs, and hangovers, and journeys and opera and hugs and friends and more alcohols, and passing out on a buddabag like the olden days, and food and food and food and singing, and karaoke booths and cocktails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So, I was in New York last week, and saw Wall Street fall over</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/so-i-was-in-new-york-last-week-and-saw-wall-street-fall-over/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 02:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/so-i-was-in-new-york-last-week-and-saw-wall-street-fall-over/</guid>
      <description>Well, sort of. I&amp;nbsp;was staying just off Wall Street, with my Very Good, Kind and Wonderful friend Artemis. It was mostly a relatively chilled-out time, but there were some bits that ended up being unexpectedly mental.
**
The stuff I did that was awesome:**
Go see Spamalot.
Go to the top of the Rockefeller Building.
Go to Mars Bar on 1st St and 2nd Avenue &amp;#8211; so long as you think that an excellent jukebox, a dingy interior, weird patrons and a stink of piss in the toilets is a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t trust strangers to make you happy.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dont-trust-strangers-to-make-you-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2008 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dont-trust-strangers-to-make-you-happy/</guid>
      <description>Strangers are funny old things.
Last night I was flitting merrily between two groups of people in Angel Lane as I prefer to do (it stops people getting tired of me), when I was suddenly transfixed mid-flit by an amazingly awesome Tshirt. The shirt in question bore the legend &amp;#8220;Bouli Bouli. Fear sneachta bán&amp;#8221; and a picture of said loveable snowman.
I let out a shout of joy and began to regale the wearer of said tshirt with my story about how Bouli used to sleep on my couch sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiding out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hiding-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2008 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/hiding-out/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m back home, hiding out for a bit. But there are definitely upsides.
Me: Dad, I need an onion.
Dad: There are loads.
Me: Where? I can&amp;#8217;t see them.
Dad: Up in the garden, go pull one.
😀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got my passport stamped in Burgerland</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/i-got-my-passport-stamped-in-burgerland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2008 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/i-got-my-passport-stamped-in-burgerland/</guid>
      <description>Last night, at a lovely barbeque at Dave and Joan&amp;#8217;s to celebrate Mister Dave&amp;#8217;s birthday, I put Hellman&amp;#8217;s Burger Sauce on my burger for the first time. I didn&amp;#8217;t know that time machine transporters came in burger sauce flavour, but they sure as hell do, because when I opened my eyes after that first bite, I was sitting on a green leatherette couch with mirrors on the walls in Burgerland on William Street.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>what-ifs?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/what-ifs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2008 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/what-ifs/</guid>
      <description>I had never seen Before Sunrise before tonight. Judge me all you like, but it&amp;#8217;s the truth. Last weekend I was in Dublin for a gig and to visit some friends, one of whom hid it on another friend&amp;#8217;s bookshelf and then texted me once he&amp;#8217;d left to give me a clue that it was there. He probably didn&amp;#8217;t want to get caught trafficing sappy films or something. He&amp;#8217;d mentioned it to me recently, and said that it seemed like the kind of film I&amp;#8217;d enjoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harry Potter and the End of the World (I’m done now, I swear!)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/harry-potter-and-the-end-of-the-world-im-done-now-i-swear/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2007 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/harry-potter-and-the-end-of-the-world-im-done-now-i-swear/</guid>
      <description>It’s been fun, since Saturday, waiting for people to finish The Book That Shall Not Be Named so that we could huddle in dark corners to discuss it without hysterical accusations of spoiling. I even set up an IRC channel on intersocs, and people have been dribbling in, saying “I can’t believe it’s over” and then leaving.
It’s odd. There are so many books out there, so many series of books, some of which are awful, but many of which are as good, and some of which are a LOT better than the Harry Potter series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obligatory, pretty much, Harry Potter Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/obligatory-pretty-much-harry-potter-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/obligatory-pretty-much-harry-potter-post/</guid>
      <description>In a bizarre turn-up for the books, it’s raining again. I’ve never been particularly bothered by the lack of summery weather before, but there’s something so depressing about the almost inevitable fact that everything this summer is going to get rained out and ruined.
I’m still finding it difficult to feel sorry for the people apparently queuing outside Eason’s bookshop since this morning in order to get their hands on the new Harry Potter book when it comes out at MinutePastMidnightO’Clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh to be a cat-lady…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oh-to-be-a-cat-lady/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2007 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oh-to-be-a-cat-lady/</guid>
      <description>Gin and Tonics in the Locke Bar on a Tuesday, whatever the reason, are a bloody good idea. I&amp;rsquo;m a fan, so long as there&amp;rsquo;s someone there to drive me home. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure when I went from thinking that Gin and Tonic was a crazy cat lady drink to thinking that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing quite so refreshing as a G&amp;amp;T with a wedge of lime, and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be lovely to have a little house for myself, and a kitten or two to keep me company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some things I just thought of that have made me happy lately</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/some-things-i-just-thought-of-that-have-made-me-happy-lately/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2007 04:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/some-things-i-just-thought-of-that-have-made-me-happy-lately/</guid>
      <description>Cake, both the making and the eating thereof.
Ciara, Maeves, Seamie, Liselle, Gar. Friends from what feels like the olden days that I&amp;#8217;ve reconnected with lately. It&amp;#8217;s been great.
Death Cab for Cutie &amp;#8211; I will follow you into the dark
My room&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; It is full of pretty things and my bass and bass amp.
My housemates in general&amp;nbsp;&amp;#8211; all six of them are adorable in different ways
Elephants over the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Kiwi Nostalgia…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/more-kiwi-nostalgia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2006 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/more-kiwi-nostalgia/</guid>
      <description>It wasn&amp;#8217;t really coffee, but I actually liked the taste of it&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve had a couple of mugs of the most instant-est, muckest, lowest-grade Nescafé instant coffee today and it tastes and smells exactly like&amp;nbsp;this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You complete me….</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/you-complete-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2006 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/you-complete-me/</guid>
      <description>I am, of course, talking about my phone.
There&amp;#8217;s a lot of guff about how bad phones are for your social interactions etc. But there&amp;#8217;s no getting away from the fact that we no longer set a definite arrangement to meet someone days in advance, we just text them or ring them to set something up, and refine the arrangement as we go.
I&amp;#8217;ve been phoneless for the past week, and I&amp;#8217;ve felt it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This weekend I…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/908/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/908/</guid>
      <description>Went on a three-pub pub crawl without a single drop of alchohol (in about an hour total). Curled up in a giggling ball on the floor of my kitchen, chewing two slices of toast as fast as I could while paul tried to take them out of my mouth with a spoon. Read about sailing the seven seas and wanted to really badly. Cleaned my house, LOTS. Put on a successful gig (huzzah and thanks) Saw a sign in Beneton&amp;#8217;s window that said &amp;#8220;All Ladies €20 or Less&amp;#8221; Scared many many people with my astoundingly good Shakira impressing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memo to self</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/memo-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2006 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/memo-to-self/</guid>
      <description>I am the master of my days.
I forget this quite a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eric Idle Fathered by Short-Lived Military Prodigy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eric-idle-fathered-by-short-lived-military-prodigy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2005 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eric-idle-fathered-by-short-lived-military-prodigy/</guid>
      <description>From IMDB:
&amp;#8220;Eric&amp;#8217;s father, who served in the Royal Air Force, died in a car crash on Christmas eve when he was two years old.&amp;#8221;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back in the day…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/back-in-the-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/back-in-the-day/</guid>
      <description>Back when I was doing my Work Experience subtitling weird kids TV shows and Survivor for Irish Language Television (yes, i actually did), I used to spend a phenomenal amount of time on the internet. On a dial-up. When local calls aren&amp;#8217;t actually free in Ireland. And they didn&amp;#8217;t really mind. I can only remember about three times when I was actually on time for work, but nobody every said anything to me about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Year in Review…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2005 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Doing the Year In Review thing, where you take the first sentence from the first entry you post each month&amp;#8230; I start the year out by getting dumped and finish it by getting smacked in the face by a prawn. In the middle, there are witches and princesses and bugger. But it&amp;#8217;s really boring.
January: Single again. I was going to say alone again, but i think i was alone before anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliments of the Season!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/649/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2004 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/649/</guid>
      <description>Well, belated compliments of the season to one and all. Whatever season you may find yourself experiencing.
Being home has been generally fantastic, with spots of less-than-fantastic. Christmas dinner was the high point. My mum finally gave in to some subtle manipulation and agreed that a Proper Turkey Dinner (with mother&amp;#8217;s amazing potato stuffing) would be a good idea, and she also had the great idea of having my gran over as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/648/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2004 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/648/</guid>
      <description>Being at home is hugely strange, and amazingly good. My brother arrived this morning, so now my little family is complete. The parents were so glad to see both of us, and I was so glad to see both of them. I don&amp;#8217;t want to stay, although I&amp;#8217;m already dreading the journey back, but it&amp;#8217;s bloody good to be home for a while anyway. Saturday was spent shopping with mum and visiting my gran, who was also super-happy to see me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/647/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2004 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/647/</guid>
      <description>At Singapore. Transitting through to Dubai. Have already stopped at brisbane. I wanna be at HOME! and it&amp;#8217;s gonna be about 23 hours from what I can see&amp;#8230; WAAAAAAH!
Don&amp;#8217;t ever do this flight in one go. It&amp;#8217;s mental!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/so-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2004 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/so-4/</guid>
      <description>This morning I decided to take a sickie from work because I was tired and not feeling the best. So I called in sick, changed my doctor&amp;#8217;s appointment to today and crawled back to bed. Whereupon the phone rang. It was my dad, telling me that my grandfather had died. I still don&amp;#8217;t know when exactly. And I&amp;#8217;m not exactly sure of the details except that he was out on the farm, picking apples on a lovely November day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full of words, devoid of thought.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/full-of-words-devoid-of-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2004 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/full-of-words-devoid-of-thought/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I did the blogging thing, I&amp;#8217;ve been doing more or less the same things, talking to the same people, working the same jobs, complaining about the same things. Three jobs is too many. Therefore from the 31st, I shall be a woman with a mere TWO jobs. the daytime one and the sometimes cleaning one are all that will be left to me. With the free time I get as a prize for removing a chunk of my income I plan to do things, write things, keep in contact with people, get some exercise and fresh air, go places, read more, meet more people and have more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weird and Wonderful Art of Text Messaging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weird-and-wonderful-art-of-text-messaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2004 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weird-and-wonderful-art-of-text-messaging/</guid>
      <description>Other people&amp;#8217;s lives live in my phone.
&amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m crazy about you and always have been. and now i&amp;#8217;ll be too ashamed to talk to you again so bye&amp;#8221;
&amp;#8220;Restricted Environmental Situational Technique&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;
&amp;#8220;It&amp;#8217;s a girl! 4.30am. caesarean&amp;#8230; 7lb6oz&amp;#8221;
&amp;#8220;Froodie, we were just talking about you and we came to the conclusion that you are all woman. Congratulations!&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; my brother&amp;#8217;s friends.
&amp;#8220;Froodie just dumped me! being nice to her = being walked on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Messiest Country in the World?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-messiest-country-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2004 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-messiest-country-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>My mum and I got all civic spirited yesterday and went for a walk&amp;#8230;
with rubber gloves and black plastic sacks in tow.
On a single 150metre (possibly less) stretch of road, we managed to fill THREE bags.
So our bin at home is full now, and I&amp;#8217;m betting the stretch of road we managed to tidy looks like shite again.
Oh, and a press 22 photographer passed us and took our photos for the local papers (cringe)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brother the Hero</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/my-brother-the-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2003 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-brother-the-hero/</guid>
      <description>I had quite an uneventful saturday night. I was supposed to go out, but my mother decided I looked too tired and she was probably right. In any case, she&amp;#8217;s footing the bill for my new glasses, so i figured it was best to keep on her good side.
Anyway, Eurovision. Yes. I watched from about the seventh song, maybe earlier. All the way to the bitter end. We were crap.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>