<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dublin on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/dublin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dublin on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/dublin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Look mom, I made an app! – Rails Girls Dublin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 00:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/look-mom-i-made-an-app-rails-girls-dublin/</guid>
      <description>[][1]Happy Rails Girls (and boys) after the workshop Photo by Serena Fritsch I&amp;#8217;m someone who has enjoyed the company of programmers for years. I consider myself relatively tech-savvy, and have played around with building simple webpages and hacking on macros using visual basic. I&amp;#8217;ve never managed to make the leap to actually “learning how to code”, despite tipping my toe in the water now and then.
I finally took the plunge today by attending a Rails Girls workshop in Dublin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gael Fours – Four Roller Derby Games  in ONE DAY!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gael-fours-four-roller-derby-games-in-one-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2014 12:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gael-fours-four-roller-derby-games-in-one-day/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve ever been curious about Roller Derby, come to the Shoreline Leisure Centre in Bray this Saturday. You&amp;#8217;ll see four games &amp;#8211; including a co-ed and a men&amp;#8217;s game!
The worst thing about the increase in the popularity of roller derby in Ireland is the fact that sometimes events clash and you end up having to miss something you were really looking forward to.
Dublin Roller Derby had invited me to announce at their upcoming double-header against Newcastle Roller Derby&amp;#8217;s Canny Belters and Hull&amp;#8217;s Angels Roller Dames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Ship Jobseeker – To intern or not to intern?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-good-ship-jobseeker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-good-ship-jobseeker/</guid>
      <description>I sent this poster off with a recent application. I&amp;#8217;ll let you know how it goes 🙂 Applying for a job? There are many of us in the job application boat at the moment, and some are dealing with it better than others. I find it absolutely gut-wrenching to put myself forward to be accepted or rejected. I absolutely hate doing it, but I&amp;#8217;ve been out of work now since I took redundancy in September, so it&amp;#8217;s time to pimp myself out to prospective employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflection, roots and rapid-fire ideas.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reflection-roots-and-rapid-fire-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2012 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reflection-roots-and-rapid-fire-ideas/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s official. I&amp;#8217;m finally a Dubliner (or whatever it is that real Dublin people call blow-ins from down the country). I&amp;#8217;ve handed back the keys to my lovely apartment in Limerick and torn up as many Limerick roots as I can, or want to (Ancór and Limerick Roller Girls 4 LYFE!). I now live in The Smoke that is bigger than the other Smokes on this tiny island. I am cohabiting with Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting around Dublin: three essential Android apps…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-around-dublin-three-essential-android-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 12:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-around-dublin-three-essential-android-apps/</guid>
      <description>So, you’ve just moved to Dublin and you’re trying to make sense of the public transport system. Don’t bother. The two Luas lines, the bus system and the Dart and rail systems are all pretty much independent of each other.Leap Card
What I recommend you do &amp;#8211; get yourself a Leap card. The fares are a little cheaper, you don’t have to worry about carrying cash, and it’ll work on all public transport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Start Continues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-new-start-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 16:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-new-start-continues/</guid>
      <description>Change is good, right?
&amp;nbsp;
I’ve changed a LOT of things in the last six weeks. I’ve moved city, shacked up with my lovely man, left my job of six years (on and off, mostly on) and started a course in Digital Marketing with a view to a career change.
  It’s been a period of rushing, rearranging and reviewing. I’ve gotten used to the DART timetables and using my Leap card (which I’ve had since I lived in Limerick &amp;#8211; very early adopter indeed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiwi Nostalgia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/924/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2006 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/924/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been thinking a lot about New Zealand since I came to Dublin. Memories keep bobbing to the surface of my mind when I least expect them to. I&amp;#8217;m dreaming about situations that did or could have taken place, following conversations to what could have been their conclusion, closing my eyes and seeing myself sitting on the verandah of the hostel in Okarito as the sun went down, drinking hot chocolate in Katipo, going to McDonalds in Auckland in the middle of the night with Legoboy, running away from some boy I&amp;#8217;d kissed on Stewart Island to go looking at the clearest sky and the brightest stars I&amp;#8217;d ever seen, trying to fly my kite the park in Christchurch and eventually succeeding.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>