<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>backpacking on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/backpacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in backpacking on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 15:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/backpacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>No sXe for me!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/762/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2005 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/762/</guid>
      <description>I will never be straightedge.
Hooray for going to random parties with a bottle of cider.
Hooray for slint-core australian bands.
Hooray for creating folk-song-singing monsters and flame-throwing monsters merely through conversation.
Hooray for all the kids I ever met in Auckland being at this party.
Hooray for sending texts to yourself because it&amp;#8217;s free.
Slightly less hooray for wigging out a little and walking home.
And then HOORAY again for legoboy rescuing me and then going for burgers and crashing out in his room watching family guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oh what a day!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oh-what-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2005 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oh-what-a-day/</guid>
      <description>Talk about birdwatching!! I just had the most fantastic day out the Otago Peninsula&amp;#8230; We saw oystercatchers, paradise shell ducks, shags, herons, a kingfisher, LOADS of albatross, lil blue penguins and yellow-eyed penguins (hoiho). Also many fur seals. The Albatross is the most amazing bird. Its chest isn&amp;#8217;t strong enough to flap its wings very much, and yet it can fly 150,000 kilometres in a YEAR! It&amp;#8217;s so graceful and dignified and amazing to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Bagpipes Batman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/holy-bagpipes-batman/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte and I were just wandering around town, checking out secondhand bookshops and having coffee and being exhausted and stuff, and then BAM, the octagon is filled with HORDES of bagpipers. there&amp;#8217;s some kind of competition on today I think.
THe best bit was at the end where about eight bands lined up together and all marched down George St playing Scotland the Brave. Stirring indeed. No matter who you are or where you&amp;#8217;re from, a bazillion bagpipers going right past your ear is an unforgettable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elusive Dunedin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/672/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2005 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/672/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t quite seem to get a handle on Dunedin. I&amp;#8217;m not sure why, but it sort of eludes me. Maybe it&amp;#8217;s because most of the students aren&amp;#8217;t here, and there are usually around 25,000 of them? I&amp;#8217;m not sure, but I think I could possibly like this town, once I get the hang of it.
Granted, it took me a lot longer than four days to get the hang of Auckland, but this place is so much smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Chinese New Year!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/happy-chinese-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2005 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/happy-chinese-new-year/</guid>
      <description>I completely forgot about the pancakes yesterday, but last night at midnight there were the coolest fireworks to celebrate Chinese New Year. It&amp;#8217;s good that NZ sometimes remembers that it&amp;#8217;s closer to Asia than Europe. Also yesterday I wandered around the Museum, which was partially closed due to flooding from the excellent rains the day before. As were quite a few shops in the city centre.
I would say more, but I&amp;#8217;m sure you don&amp;#8217;t care that it was a little bit chilly last night, that I had tuna and cheese on toast for dinner or that I did my laundry and watched survivor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Again with the Dunedin and the Sunshine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/again-with-the-dunedin-and-the-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2005 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/again-with-the-dunedin-and-the-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday was moderately uneventful, except that when I left the internet cafe there was a massive black cloud obscuring all light, and I eventually got caught in the mother of all downpours. It was great. Thunder, lightening, massive raindrops and rivers instead of streets! I got back to the hostel and was so soaking wet that I put my bag down and ran straight back out again.
Fantastic!
Today I got offered a lift to invercargill with two swiss chicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dunedin, Sunshine and Dreamcatchers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dunedin-sunshine-and-dreamcatchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2005 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dunedin-sunshine-and-dreamcatchers/</guid>
      <description>Good afternoon,
Yesterday I arrived in Dunedin, proceeded to get lost, (which is never a good idea with a backpack that&amp;#8217;s too heavy), get found, went online to check my mail and update here, couldn&amp;#8217;t check my mail cos none of the websites would open, managed to open LJ and typed up a major updatey post on getting drunk and misbehaving, leaving christchurch, lake tekapo and the unbelievable gorgeousness, oamaru and limestone and small-town-ness and penguins and tour buses, and weird nightmares about fountains and collapsing buildings, and tried to post it and it died, which was the computer&amp;#8217;s fault, not mine&amp;#8230; and i had to pay $4 for the privilege of NOT BEING ABLE TO CHECK MY MAIL and GETTING UPSET THAT MY UPDATE GOT EATEN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So…</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/so-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2004 21:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/so-4/</guid>
      <description>This morning I decided to take a sickie from work because I was tired and not feeling the best. So I called in sick, changed my doctor&amp;#8217;s appointment to today and crawled back to bed. Whereupon the phone rang. It was my dad, telling me that my grandfather had died. I still don&amp;#8217;t know when exactly. And I&amp;#8217;m not exactly sure of the details except that he was out on the farm, picking apples on a lovely November day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November in Summer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2004 22:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/628/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s funny to think that it&amp;#8217;s November-y back home. Here it&amp;#8217;s summer holiday weather. We sat outside O&amp;#8217;Carrolls, an Irish bar, for a few hours this evening, in t-shirts or string tops, and jandals. Myself, Caroline, Liz and Gary and Phil decided to bring lots of randoms along to the pub with us. So we were joined by what turned out to be 5 Hot Guys.
😀
Which was nice!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh! November!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2004 19:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/oh-november/</guid>
      <description>Buggerit! I really am working for the man. GE donated $2.58million to the US Republican party since 1999. Yuk. I&amp;#8217;m finishing in 2 weeks though, so that&amp;#8217;ll stick it to them. Yeah! And I stole about 20 helium balloons today, all printed with GE Money, which is what GE finance is now called in New Zealand. So I&amp;#8217;ve made them scared now, I&amp;#8217;ll bet.
In other news, there has been much fun and also some sleep had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pterry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/626/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2004 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/626/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m going to see Terry Pratchett on Sunday.
By saturday evening, I will have one less job.
Life is definitely getting there!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full of words, devoid of thought.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/full-of-words-devoid-of-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2004 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/full-of-words-devoid-of-thought/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time I did the blogging thing, I&amp;#8217;ve been doing more or less the same things, talking to the same people, working the same jobs, complaining about the same things. Three jobs is too many. Therefore from the 31st, I shall be a woman with a mere TWO jobs. the daytime one and the sometimes cleaning one are all that will be left to me. With the free time I get as a prize for removing a chunk of my income I plan to do things, write things, keep in contact with people, get some exercise and fresh air, go places, read more, meet more people and have more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>