<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>opinion on niria.in</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in opinion on niria.in</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Therapy: Part 2 – The Drugs sometimes Work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/adventures-in-therapy-part-2-the-drugs-sometimes-work/</guid>
      <description>This is the second post in my series on the topic of the different treatments I&amp;#8217;ve been on for Depression &amp; Anxiety. I&amp;#8217;m looking at the different types of drugs I was prescribed and I might also tell you how I really feel about people&amp;#8217;s attitude to medicating for depression. Before I say anything else, a disclaimer. These are the drugs I was prescribed, these are the effects and side-effects I personally had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Street Harassment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2013 00:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/on-street-harassment/</guid>
      <description>I stood up to a street harasser yesterday and I&amp;#8217;m glad I did. Here&amp;#8217;s a fuller version of the story.
First, some context:
A train full of people returning from a sporting event is an experience. I got the train from Limerick to Dublin yesterday and the first leg was full of Cork and Limerick supporters on their way home. I was on the train 15 minutes before departure and there were only a few empty seats dotted around the carriages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Ship Jobseeker – To intern or not to intern?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-good-ship-jobseeker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-good-ship-jobseeker/</guid>
      <description>I sent this poster off with a recent application. I&amp;#8217;ll let you know how it goes 🙂 Applying for a job? There are many of us in the job application boat at the moment, and some are dealing with it better than others. I find it absolutely gut-wrenching to put myself forward to be accepted or rejected. I absolutely hate doing it, but I&amp;#8217;ve been out of work now since I took redundancy in September, so it&amp;#8217;s time to pimp myself out to prospective employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s in a name?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/whats-in-a-name-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 16:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/whats-in-a-name-2/</guid>
      <description>[][1]Image by [bump][2] It&amp;#8217;s been quite a journey to figure out who I am. On my birth cert, my name is Sarah Ann Ryan. I read Anne of Green Gables as a kid and began insisting on the E at the end of Ann &amp;#8211; why wouldn&amp;#8217;t you? My secondary school operated through the medium of the Irish language and insisted I use the full translation of both of my names &amp;#8211; Sorcha Ní Riain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weltschmertz from an atheist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/weltschmertz-from-an-atheist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 23:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/weltschmertz-from-an-atheist/</guid>
      <description>Some days I wish I believed in God. After hearing of the events in Connecticut today, this is one of those days. Today, faith would give me both someone to rail against, and would give me solace and comfort in the thought that those murdered had eternal souls, or a chance at rebirth.
Instead, I’m confronted with the bleak reality that a human person was either born or became so damaged that they could murder their family, along with innocent children and adults.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>